A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.1, Series 100 International - Series 257 Virgin Islands, U.S.A. FA386a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1909-1974; 200; 28 Cubic Feet; 69 __Boxes __28 cubic feet
  - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1922-1972; 200.R; 43 Cubic Feet; 108 __Boxes __43 cubic feet
    - Chinese History, 1937-1942 (Box 216, Folder 2588)
    - Chinese History, 1937-1942 (Box 216, Folder 2589)
    - Chinese History, 1943-1962 (Box 217, Folder 2590)
    - Chinese History, 1943-1962 (Box 217, Folder 2591)
    - Chinese History, 1943-1962 (Box 217, Folder 2592)
    - Chinese History, 1943-1962 (Box 217, Folder 2593)
    - Chinese History, 1943-1962 (Box 217, Folder 2594)
    - Chinese History, 1943-1962 (Box 217, Folder 2595)
    - Chinese History - Reprints, 1939-1956 (Box 217, Folder 2596)
    - Civilian Conservation Corps - Survey, 1935 (Box 217, Folder 2597)
    - Civilian Conservation Corps - Survey - Reports, 1935; 5 Items (Box 217, Folder 2598)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies, 1935-1939 (Box 217, Folder 2599)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies, 1935-1939 (Box 217, Folder 2600)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies, 1935-1939 (Box 217, Folder 2601)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies, 1940-1954 (Box 218, Folder 2602)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies, 1940-1954 (Box 218, Folder 2603)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies, 1940-1954 (Box 218, Folder 2604)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies, 1940-1954 (Box 218, Folder 2605)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies, 1940-1954 (Box 218, Folder 2606)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies, 1940-1954 (Box 218, Folder 2607)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies - Reports, 1944-1946; 4 Items (Box 218, Folder 2608)
    - Claremont Colleges - Far Eastern Studies - Reprints and Pamphlets, 1946-1949; 8 Items (Box 218, Folder 2609)
    - Claremont Colleges - Indian Art, April 1936-1938 (Box 218, Folder 2610)
    - Claremont Colleges - Indian Art, April 1936-1938 (Box 218, Folder 2611)
    - Claremont Colleges - Indian Art - Pamphlets, 1936; 4 Items (Box 218, Folder 2612)
    - Code, Grant H. - (Problems of the Artist - Study), 1939-1941, 1951 (Box 218, Folder 2613)
    - Code, Grant H. - (Problems of the Artist - Study), 1939-1941, 1951 (Box 218, Folder 2614)
    - Code, Grant H. - (Problems of the Artist - Study) - Report, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 2615)
    - Colgate University - Religion, 1943-1951 (Box 219, Folder 2616)
    - Colgate University - Religion - Report, 1944 (Box 219, Folder 2617)
    - College of William and Mary - Jefferson, Adams - Letters, 1948-1949 (Box 219, Folder 2618)
    - College of William and Mary - Theatre, 1942-1948 (Box 219, Folder 2619)
    - College of William and Mary - Theatre - Pamphlet, 1947 (Box 219, Folder 2620)
    - Colorado School of Mines - English Language Teaching, 1943-1949 (Box 219, Folder 2621)
    - Colorado School of Mines - English Language Teaching, 1943-1949 (Box 219, Folder 2622)
    - Columbia University - Brunner, Edmund de S. - (Study of Agricultural Extension), 1934-1938 (Box 219, Folder 2623)
    - Columbia University - Brunner, Edmund de S. - (Study of Agricultural Extension), 1950 (Box 219, Folder 2624)
    - Columbia University - Brunner - Report by Marjorie Patten - "Keeping Culture in Agriculture", 1937 (Box 219, Folder 2625)
    - Columbia University - Brunner - Report by Marjorie Patten - "Keeping Culture in Agriculture", 1937 (Box 219, Folder 2626)
    - Columbia University - Chinese Library, 1937-1944 (Box 220, Folder 2627)
    - Columbia University - Chinese Library, 1937-1944 (Box 220, Folder 2628)
    - Columbia University - Chinese Library - Report, 1942 (Box 220, Folder 2629)
    - Columbia University - Chinese Literature, 1942-1948 (Box 220, Folder 2630)
    - Columbia University - Chinese Religion and Philosophy, 1944-1948 (Box 220, Folder 2631)
    - Columbia University - Drama, 1934-1940 (Box 220, Folder 2632)
    - Columbia University - Drama - Pamphlets, 1938-1940 (Box 220, Folder 2633)
    - Columbia University - Drama - Pamphlets, 1938-1940 (Box 220, Folder 2633)
    - Columbia University - Drama, 1947-1949 (Box 220, Folder 2634)
    - Columbia University - English Usage, 1934-1944 (Box 220, Folder 2635)
    - Columbia University - English Usage, 1934-1944 (Box 220, Folder 2636)
    - Columbia University - English Usage - Reports, 1937-1938 (Box 220, Folder 2637)
    - Columbia University - Far Eastern Studies, 1939-1948 (Box 220, Folder 2638)
    - Columbia University - Far Eastern Studies, 1939-1948 (Box 220, Folder 2639)
    - Columbia University - Far Eastern Studies, 1939-1948 (Box 220, Folder 2640)
    - Columbia University - Far Eastern Studies, 1939-1948 (Box 220, Folder 2641)
    - Columbia University - Humanities, 1929-1940 (Box 221, Folder 2642)
    - Columbia University - Humanities, 1957 (Box 221, Folder 2643)
    - Columbia University - Humanities, 1929-1940 (Box 221, Folder 2644)
    - Columbia University - Humanities, 1957 (Box 221, Folder 2645)
    - Columbia University - Humanities - Base Record, 1939 (Box 221, Folder 2646)
    - Columbia University - Humanities, 1930-1936; 6 items contained in folders 2647-2648. (Box 221, Folder 2647)
    - Columbia University - Humanities, 1930-1936; 6 items contained in folders 2647-2648. (Box 221, Folder 2648)
    - Columbia University - Japanese Grammar, 1943-1948 (Box 221, Folder 2649)
    - Columbia University - Portugese Language Studies, 1942-1948 (Box 221, Folder 2650)
    - Columbia University - Portugese Language Studies - Reports (Published), 1943-1944; 3 items (Box 221, Folder 2651)
    - Columbia University - Public Opinion, 1940-1942 (Box 221, Folder 2652)
    - Columbia University - Public Opinion, 1940-1942 (Box 221, Folder 2653)
    - Columbia University - Radio Listening - Children, 1940-1942 (Box 221, Folder 2654)
    - Columbia University - Radio Listening - Children, 1940-1942 (Box 221, Folder 2655)
    - Columbia University - Radio Listening - Children - Report, 1941 (Box 221, Folder 2656)
    - Columbia University - Radio Listening - Maps, 1940-1942 (Box 222, Folder 2657)
    - Columbia University - Radio Listening - Maps, 1940-1942 (Box 222, Folder 2658)
    - Columbia University - Radio Listening - Maps, 1940; 3 items (Box 222, Folder 2659)
    - Columbia University - Radio Speech, 1936-1938 (Box 222, Folder 2660)
    - Columbia University - Radio Study, 1939-1948 (Box 222, Folder 2661)
    - Columbia University - Radio Study, 1939-1948 (Box 222, Folder 2662)
    - Columbia University - Radio Study, 1939-1948 (Box 222, Folder 2663)
    - Columbia University - Radio Study, 1939-1948 (Box 222, Folder 2664)
    - Columbia University - Radio Study, 1939-1948 (Box 222, Folder 2665)
    - Columbia University - Radio Study, 1939-1948 (Box 222, Folder 2666)
    - Columbia University - Radio Study, 1939-1948 (Box 222, Folder 2667)
    - Columbia University - Radio Study - Reports, 1939-1941; 4 items contained in folders 2668-2669. (Box 223, Folder 2668)
    - Columbia University - Radio Study - Reports, 1939-1941; 4 items contained in folders 2668-2669. (Box 223, Folder 2669)
    - Columbia University - Sioux Language Study, 1934-1935 (Box 223, Folder 2670)
    - Columbia University - Taubenschlag, Rafael - (Refugee Scholar, Classics), 1942-1952 (Box 223, Folder 2671)
    - Communications Research, 1939-July 1940 (Box 223, Folder 2672)
    - Communications Research, 1939-July 1940 (Box 223, Folder 2673)
    - Communications Research, August 1940-1942 (Box 224, Folder 2674)
    - Communications Research, August 1940-1942 (Box 224, Folder 2675)
    - Communications Research, August 1940-1942 (Box 224, Folder 2676)
    - Communications Research - Report - (Section 1-2 and Incomplete Duplicate), 1939 (Box 224, Folder 2677)
    - Communications Research - Report - (Section 1-2 and Incomplete Duplicate), 1939 (Box 224, Folder 2678)
    - Communications Research - Report - (Section 1-2 and Incomplete Duplicate), 1939 (Box 224, Folder 2679)
    - Communications Research - Working Papers, 1939-1940; 6 items (Box 224, Folder 2680)
    - Conference on American Thought, February 1944-1945 (Box 224, Folder 2681)
    - Conference on American Thought, February 1944-1945 (Box 224, Folder 2682)
    - Conference on American Thought, February 1944-1945 (Box 224, Folder 2683)
    - Conference on American Thought - Memorandums, 1944 (Box 224, Folder 2684)
    - Conference on American Thought - Transcript, 1944 (Box 225, Folder 2685)
    - Conference on American Thought - Transcript, 1944 (Box 225, Folder 2686)
    - Conference on Far Eastern Studies, 1940 (Box 225, Folder 2687)
    - Conference on Far Eastern Studies in the Pacific Area, February 1944-1945 (Box 225, Folder 2688)
    - Conference on Far Eastern Studies in the Pacific Area, February 1944-1945 (Box 225, Folder 2689)
    - Conference on Far Eastern Studies in the Pacific Area - Report, 1944 (Box 225, Folder 2690)
    - Conference on Speech in Radio, 1937-1938 (Box 226, Folder 2691)
    - Conference on Speech in Radio - Report, 1937 (Box 226, Folder 2692)
    - Connecticut College - German Studies, 1943-1949 (Box 226, Folder 2693)
    - Connecticut College - German Studies, 1943-1949 (Box 226, Folder 2694)
    - Cornell University - Cultural History, 1941-1949 (Box 226, Folder 2695)
    - Cornell University - Cultural History - Report, 1943 (Box 226, Folder 2696)
    - Cornell University - Cultural History - Pamphlets, 1943-1944 (Box 226, Folder 2697)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music), 1933-1941 (Box 226, Folder 2698)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music), 1933-1941 (Box 226, Folder 2699)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music), 1933-1941 (Box 226, Folder 2700)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music), 1933-1941 (Box 226, Folder 2701)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music), 1933-1941 (Box 226, Folder 2702)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music), 1933-1941 (Box 226, Folder 2703)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music), 1942-1949 (Box 227, Folder 2704)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music), 1942-1949 (Box 227, Folder 2705)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music) - Report, 1939 (Box 227, Folder 2706)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music) - Reports and Pamphlets, 1935-1942; 5 items contained in folders 2707-2708. (Box 227, Folder 2707)
    - Cornell University - Drama (and Music) - Reports and Pamphlets, 1935-1942; 5 items contained in folders 2707-2708. (Box 227, Folder 2708)
    - Cornell University - Drama, 1964-1967 (Box 227, Folder 2709)
    - Cornell University - Far Eastern Studies, 1938-1958 (Box 227, Folder 2710)
    - Cornell University - Far Eastern Studies, 1938-1958 (Box 227, Folder 2711)
    - Cornell University - Far Eastern Studies, 1938-1958 (Box 227, Folder 2712)
    - Cornell University - Far Eastern Studies - Reprints, 1957-1958; 2 items (Box 227, Folder 2713)
    - Cornell University - Regional Studies, 1941-1949 (Box 228, Folder 2714)
    - Cornell University - Regional Studies, 1941-1949 (Box 228, Folder 2715)
    - Cornell University - Regional Studies - Pamphlets, 1942; 2 items (Box 228, Folder 2716)
    - Cornell University - Russian Studies, June 1943-1959 (Box 228, Folder 2717)
    - Cornell University - Russian Studies, June 1943-1959 (Box 228, Folder 2718)
    - Cornell University - Russian Studies, June 1943-1959 (Box 228, Folder 2719)
    - Cornell University - Russian Studies, July-1943-1950 (Box 229, Folder 2720)
    - Cornell University - Russian Studies, July-1943-1950 (Box 229, Folder 2721)
    - Cornell University - Russian Studies, July-1943-1950 (Box 229, Folder 2722)
    - Cornell University - Russian Studies, July-1943-1950 (Box 229, Folder 2723)
    - Cornell University - Russian Studies, 1943-1944; 3 items (Box 229, Folder 2724)
    - Cornell University - Russian Studies - Pamphlets, 1942-1943; 3 items (Box 229, Folder 2725)
    - Dance Survey, 1948-1949 (Box 229, Folder 2726)
    - De Los Rios, Fernando - (Refugee Scholar, Social And Political Science, New School for Social Research), 1939-1945 (Box 229, Folder 2727)
    - De Los Rios, Fernando - (Refugee Scholar, Social And Political Science, New School for Social Research), 1939-1945 (Box 229, Folder 2728)
    - Drama Conference, 1934 (Box 229, Folder 2729)
    - Drama Survey - Schnitzer, Robert, 1948 (Box 229, Folder 2730)
    - Duke University - Dubs, Homer H. - (Chinese History Translation), 1937-1938 (Box 229, Folder 2731)
    - Duke University - Folklore Collection, 1944-1954 (Box 229, Folder 2732)
    - Duke University - Microphotography, 1941-1942 (Box 229, Folder 2733)
    - Duke University - Microphotography, 1941-1942 (Box 229, Folder 2734)
    - Engineering Societies Library, 1941-1949 (Box 230, Folder 2735)
    - Engineering Societies Library, 1941-1949 (Box 230, Folder 2736)
    - Engineering Societies Library, 1941-1949 (Box 230, Folder 2737)
    - English Teaching Conference, 1938 (Box 230, Folder 2738)
    - English Teaching Conference - Report, 1938 (Box 230, Folder 2739)
    - English Teaching Conference, 1941-1942 (Box 230, Folder 2740)
    - English Teaching Conference, 1941-1942 (Box 230, Folder 2741)
    - English Teaching Conference - Report, 1941 (Box 230, Folder 2742)
    - Field Museum of Natural History - Chinese Archaeology, 1940-1941 (Box 230, Folder 2743)
    - Fogg Art Museum - Oriental Art, 1935-1939 (Box 230, Folder 2744)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library, 1933-1942 (Box 230, Folder 2745)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library, 1933-1942 (Box 230, Folder 2746)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library - Reports, 1935-1939; 7 items (Box 230, Folder 2747)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library - Reports (Financial), 1938-1940; 3 items (Box 230, Folder 2748)
    - Fordham University - Von Hildebrand, Dietrich - (Refugee Scholar, Philosophy), 1940-1943 (Box 231, Folder 2749)
    - Fordham University - Von Hildebrand, Dietrich - (Refugee Scholar, Philosophy), 1940-1943 (Box 231, Folder 2750)
    - Fordham University - Von Hildebrand, Dietrich - (Refugee Scholar, Philosophy), 1952-1954 (Box 231, Folder 2751)
    - Free Library of Philadelphia - Congressional Documents, 1945-1952 (Box 231, Folder 2752)
    - Gest Chinese Research Library, 1927-1949 (Box 231, Folder 2753)
    - Gest Chinese Research Library, 1927-1949 (Box 231, Folder 2754)
    - Gest Chinese Research Library, 1927-1949 (Box 231, Folder 2755)
    - Gest Chinese Research Library - Report, 1939 (Box 231, Folder 2756)
    - Great Plains Studies - Smith, George, 1942; 1215018 (Box 231, Folder 2757)
    - Great Plains Studies - Smith, George - Report, 1942 (Box 231, Folder 2758)
    - Hamilton College - With - (Art), 1942-1944 (Box 231, Folder 2759)
    - Hamilton College - With - (Art) - Report, 1944 (Box 231, Folder 2760)
    - Handicrafts Survey, 1935 (Box 231, Folder 2761)
    - Handicrafts Survey - Report - "Handicrafts in Adult Education" - by Harry Beck Greene, 1935 (Box 231, Folder 2762)
    - Handicrafts Survey, 1945-1946 (Box 231, Folder 2763)
    - Handicrafts Survey, 1945-1946 (Box 231, Folder 2764)
    - Handicrafts Survey - Report - "Teacher Training in Handicrafts" - by Robert S. Whitelaw, 1945 (Box 232, Folder 2765)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation, 1934 (Box 232, Folder 2766)
    - Harvard University - Architecture, 1945-1946 (Box 232, Folder 2767)
    - Harvard University - Broadcasting, 1939-1943 (Box 232, Folder 2768)
    - Harvard University - Broadcasting, 1939-1943 (Box 232, Folder 2769)
    - Harvard University - Broadcasting, 1939-1943 (Box 232, Folder 2770)
    - Harvard University - Broadcasting - Friedrich, C. J., 1940-1944 (Box 232, Folder 2771)
    - Harvard University - Broadcasting - Friedrich, C. J., 1940-1944 (Box 232, Folder 2772)
    - Harvard University - Broadcasting - Friedrich, C. J., 1940-1944 (Box 232, Folder 2773)
    - Harvard University - Chinese Library Aid, 1943-1948 (Box 232, Folder 2774)
    - Harvard University - Chinese Library Aid - Report, 1944 (Box 232, Folder 2775)
    - Harvard University - Humanities, 1932-1940, 1946 (Box 233, Folder 2776)
    - Harvard University - Humanities, 1932-1940, 1946 (Box 233, Folder 2777)
    - Harvard University - Humanities, 1932-1940, 1946 (Box 233, Folder 2778)
    - Harvard University - Humanities, 1932-1940, 1946 (Box 233, Folder 2779)
    - Harvard University - Humanities, 1932-1940, 1946 (Box 233, Folder 2780)
    - Harvard University - Jones, Francis C. - (Far Eastern Studies), 1935-1937 (Box 233, Folder 2781)
    - Harvard University - Lednicki, Waclan - (Visiting Lecturer, Slavic Studies), 1940-1944 (Box 233, Folder 2782)
    - Harvard University - Lednicki, Waclan - (Visiting Lecturer, Slavic Studies), 1940-1944 (Box 233, Folder 2783)
    - Harvard University - Microphotography, 1938-1954 (Box 233, Folder 2784)
    - Harvard University - Microphotography, 1938-1954 (Box 233, Folder 2785)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1938-1941 (Box 233, Folder 2786)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1938-1941 (Box 233, Folder 2787)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1938-1941 (Box 233, Folder 2788)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2789)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2790)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2791)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2792)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2793)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2794)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2795)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2796)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2797)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching), 1950 (Box 235, Folder 2798)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching) - Reports, 1942-1950; 11 items contained in folders 2799-2800. (Box 235, Folder 2799)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - (English Teaching) - Reports, 1942-1950; 11 items contained in folders 2799-2800. (Box 235, Folder 2800)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - Report by Elba, Preabea - "Elementary and Secondary Education In the U.S. and Argentina", 1940 (Box 235, Folder 2801)
    - Harvard University - Richards - Report by Hazel Mae Johnson - "Methods used by Teachers of Spanish Speaking Children", 1940 (Box 235, Folder 2802)
    - Harvard University - Richards, Ivor A. - Pamphlets and Clippings, 1941-1945; 15 items (Box 235, Folder 2803)
    - Harvard - Yenching Institute - Library, 1936-1940 (Box 235, Folder 2804)
    - Harvard - Yenching Institute - Library, 1936-1940 (Box 235, Folder 2805)
    - Harvard - Yenching Institute - Library, 1947-1949 (Box 235, Folder 2806)
    - Harvard - Yenching Institute - Library - Reports and Reprints, 1933-1939; 5 items (Box 235, Folder 2807)
    - Harvard - Yenching Institute - Visiting Lecturers, 1936-1937 (Box 235, Folder 2808)
    - Harvard - Yenching Institute - Wang, 1944-1948 (Box 236, Folder 2809)
    - Houghton, Norris - (Drama), 1939-1942 (Box 236, Folder 2810)
    - Houghton, Norris - (Drama), 1939-1942 (Box 236, Folder 2811)
    - Indiana University - Folklore Institute - Mendoza, Vicente, 1946-1948 (Box 236, Folder 2812)
    - Indiana University - Folklore Institute - Mendoza, Vicente - Reports, 1946; 2 items (Box 236, Folder 2813)
    - Institute For Advanced Study - Baron, Hans - (Renaissance Studies), 1944-1949 (Box 236, Folder 2814)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Eliot, T. S. - (Literary Criticism), 1947-1949 (Box 236, Folder 2815)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Everett, Charles W. - (Edward Everett Study), 1944-1949 (Box 236, Folder 2816)
    - Institute for Advanced Study - Tedesco, Paul - (Refugee Scholar, Near East Studies), 1935-1939 (Box 236, Folder 2817)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations - Chinese Language Studies, 1934-1939 (Box 236, Folder 2818)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations - Chinese Language Studies - Report, 1936 (Box 236, Folder 2819)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations - Russian Language School, 1933-1937 (Box 236, Folder 2820)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary - Lewy, Julius - (Refugee Scholar, Semetic Studies), 1934-1939 (Box 236, Folder 2821)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Haver Collection, 1939-1940 (Box 236, Folder 2822)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Haver Collection, 1947 (Box 236, Folder 2823)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Humanities, 1929-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2824)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Humanities, 1929-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2825)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Humanities, 1929-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2826)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Humanities, 1929-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2827)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Humanities - Reports and Reprints, 1929-1942; 2 items (Box 237, Folder 2828)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Spenser Project, 1936-1940 (Box 237, Folder 2829)
    - Kenyon College - Salomon, Richard - (Refugee Scholar, Medieval History), 1942-1948 (Box 237, Folder 2830)
    - Language Teaching Conference, 1948 (Box 237, Folder 2831)
    - Language Teaching Development Committee, 1947-1949 (Box 238, Folder 2832)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (Duke University), 1940-1953 (Box 238, Folder 2833)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (Duke University), 1940-1953 (Box 238, Folder 2834)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (Duke University) - Reports, 1940-1943 (Box 238, Folder 2835)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (Duke University) - Reports, 1940-1943 (Box 238, Folder 2836)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (Tulane University), 1940-1947 (Box 238, Folder 2837)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (Tulane University), 1940-1947 (Box 238, Folder 2838)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (Tulane University) - Report, 1940 (Box 238, Folder 2839)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (University of North Carolina), 1938-1954 (Box 238, Folder 2840)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (University of North Carolina), 1938-1954 (Box 238, Folder 2841)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (University of North Carolina) - Reports, 1935-1947; 14 items contained in folders 2842-2843. (Box 238, Folder 2842)
    - Latin American Studies - Development in Southeast - (University of North Carolina) - Reports, 1935-1947; 14 items contained in folders 2842-2843. (Box 238, Folder 2843)
    - Lawrence College - Beck, Warren - (Creative Writing), 1947-1949 (Box 238, Folder 2844)
    - Lawrence College - Humanities, 1945-1949 (Box 238, Folder 2845)
    - Library of Congress - Baumgardt, David - (Refugee Scholar, Philosophy), 1941-1944 (Box 239, Folder 2846)
    - Library of Congress - Baumgardt, David - (Refugee Scholar, Philosophy), 1941-1944 (Box 239, Folder 2847)
    - Library of Congress - Catalog, 1941-1949 (Box 239, Folder 2848)
    - Library of Congress - Catalog, 1941-1949 (Box 239, Folder 2849)
    - Library of Congress - Catalog, 1941-1949 (Box 239, Folder 2850)
    - Library of Congress - Catalog - Pamphlets, 1942-1946; 2 items (Box 239, Folder 2851)
    - Library of Congress - Communications Trends, 1940-1950 (Box 239, Folder 2852)
    - Library of Congress - Communications Trends, 1940-1950 (Box 239, Folder 2853)